<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <integer-array name="info_signs_imgs">
        <item>@drawable/img_info_aries</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_taurus</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_gemini</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_cancer</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_leo</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_virgo</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_libra</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_scorpio</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_sagittarius</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_capricorn</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_aquarius</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_info_pisces</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="info_signs_intervals">
        <item>Mar 21 - Apr 19</item>
        <item>Apr 20 - May 20</item>
        <item>May 21 - Jun 20</item>
        <item>Jun 21 - Jul 22</item>
        <item>Jul 23 - Aug 22</item>
        <item>Aug 23 - Sep 22</item>
        <item>Sep 23 - Oct 22</item>
        <item>Oct 23 - Nov 21</item>
        <item>Nov 22 - Dec 21</item>
        <item>Dec 22 - Jan 19</item>
        <item>Jan 20 - Feb 18</item>
        <item>Feb 19 - Mar 20</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="info_signs_ruler">
        <item>Mars</item>
        <item>Venus</item>
        <item>Mercury</item>
        <item>Moon</item>
        <item>Sun</item>
        <item>Mercury</item>
        <item>Venus</item>
        <item>Pluto, Mars</item>
        <item>Jupiter</item>
        <item>Saturn</item>
        <item>Uranus</item>
        <item>Neptune, Jupiter</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_signs_lucky_days">
        <item>Tuesday</item>
        <item>Friday,Monday</item>
        <item>Wednesday</item>
        <item>Monday, Thursday</item>
        <item>Sunday</item>
        <item>Wednesday</item>
        <item>Friday</item>
        <item>Tuesday</item>
        <item>Thursday</item>
        <item>Saturday</item>
        <item>Saturday</item>
        <item>Thursday</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_signs_colors">
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Green, Pink</item>
        <item>Light green, Yellow</item>
        <item>White</item>
        <item>Gold, Yellow, Orange</item>
        <item>Grey, Pale-Yellow</item>
        <item>Pink, Green</item>
        <item>Red, Rust</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Brown, Black</item>
        <item>Light blue, Silver</item>
        <item>Purple, Violet, Seagreen</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_signs_quality">
        <item>Cardinal</item>
        <item>Fixed</item>
        <item>Mutable</item>
        <item>Cardinal</item>
        <item>Fixed</item>
        <item>Mutable</item>
        <item>Cardinal</item>
        <item>Fixed</item>
        <item>Mutable</item>
        <item>Cardinal</item>
        <item>Fixed</item>
        <item>Mutable</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="info_signs_element">
        <item>Fire</item>
        <item>Earth</item>
        <item>Air</item>
        <item>Water</item>
        <item>Fire</item>
        <item>Earth</item>
        <item>Air</item>
        <item>Water</item>
        <item>Fire</item>
        <item>Earth</item>
        <item>Air</item>
        <item>Water</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_signs_lucky_dates">
        <item>1, 8, 17</item>
        <item>2, 6, 9, 12, 24</item>
        <item>5, 7, 14, 23</item>
        <item>2, 3, 15, 20</item>
        <item>1, 3, 10, 19</item>
        <item>5, 14, 15, 23, 32</item>
        <item>4, 6, 13, 15, 24</item>
        <item>8, 11, 18, 22</item>
        <item>3, 7, 9, 12, 21</item>
        <item>4, 8, 13, 22</item>
        <item>4, 7, 11, 22, 29</item>
        <item>3, 9, 12, 15, 18, 24</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info_signs_description">
        <item>Ariens are famed for their fiery, positive, outgoing natures. Considered among the most enthusiastic of the zodliac children, they have high energy levels and often fast-paced lifestyles. Their fiery determination to accomplish things sometimes encourages hot-headedness and rudeness. Ariens do all things in their own way, with energetic determination and regardless of obstacles.</item>
        <item>Taureans are famed for their romanticism, reliability, and charm, and they are often reputed to be the most beautiful people among all the zodiac children. Warm and affectionate, and sincere, they inspire confidence and loyalty in those around them. Taureans have a great need for financial and personal security. They love luxury, comfort, and beautiful things — tendencies that can encourage an obsessive possessiveness on their part like the bull who symbolizes their sign, Taureans are slow to anger, but when aroused, they can be fearsome.</item>
        <item>Geminians are lively, restless, quick-witted, last thinking, mercurial creatures who rarely stay in one place — physically or philosophically — for long, They are marvelous communicators and easily sway people to their own ideas and opinions. Geminians detest boredom — indeed, they run from it — and often prefer spreading their considerable emotional and intellectual energies among a variety of tasks (and people). This ability to do several things at once is typical of the Geminians dual nature‘ aptly represented by the Twins. Poorly channeled, however, the Geminians inability to settle down with one thing or one person can lead to the appearance of shallowness and a tendency to gloss over the important details of life.</item>
        <item>Sensitive (but often “crabby“), imaginatively creative and artistically gifted (but often obsessed with the minutiae of home and the past), Cancerians are among the most challenging of the zodiac children to get to know. Like the crab that symbolizes their sign, they often present a hard, crusty, even impenetrable exterior to the world, and can appear Withdrawn, cool, and reserved. Beneath the shell, however, lies an emotional and sensitive soul with great reserves of compassion and intuition. Like the crab, Cancerians are also tenacious and protective of their home turf and make for fiercely protective and loyal parents and friends.</item>
        <item>As majestic and impressive as the Lion that represents their sign, Leos are the natural leaders of the zodiac. Radiantly enthusiastic, magnanimous with their charm and gifts, and fiercely proud and confitdent. Leos love and live life to the fullest and expect, indeed need In be at the helm at home, work, and play. Wonderfully affectionate, dramatic, and creative — there are many Leos among the actors of the world. Leos hate small-mindedness and nit-picking. But they themselves are occasionally stubborn, autocratic, and dogmatic.</item>
        <item>Virgoans are modest, self-effacing, hardworking, and practical on the surface, but are often earthy, warm, and loving beneath that surface, as befits their zodiac symbol, the Virgin, a composite figure of ancient goddesses of the earth and the harvest. Quick thinking and analytical, Virgoans have so much excess mental energy that they often are subject to stress and tension. Their merchants for perfection and hard work also incline them towards being over-critical at times. The planet Mercury (the planet of communication) rules Gemini and Virgo. Virgoans are excellent and persuasive communicators who use their keen intellects to win arguments and win over people.</item>
        <item>Outgoing, warm-hearted, and very sociable, Librans like the Scales that represent the sign, are frequently concerned with achieving balance, harmony, peace, and justice in the people and in the world around them and they are well-equipped to do that with their enormous reserves of charm, cleverness, frankness, persuasion, and easy communication. They tend at times to be too facile and laid-back and have earned an undeserved reputation for laziness. In fact, they can be hard workers and are often leaders in their fields. They are especially good at any “peace-keeping” types of jobs because they have the remarkable gift of easily seeing (and reconciling) both sides of an issue.</item>
        <item>Mysterious Scorpios are deep-thinking, private, intense, very sexual, and always a step removed from the world. Because of their intensity and an obsessive need for privacy, there is often an aura of “danger” around Scorpios a trait they share, of course, with the deadly Scorpion that symbolizes their sign. But this is only one facet of the rather complex Scorpio personality. They can be driven workers and achievers with the ability to overcome enormously challenging obstacles. They also value their intimate relationships and their friendships quite highly and work hard to encourage the best in those they love</item>
        <item>Sagittarians love challenges of all kinds — physical or mental and throw themselves into intellectual or physical pursuits with boundless and infectious reserves of energy. Sagittarians’ interests in both purely intellectual pursuits and highly physical adventure underscore their versatile natures and are clearly related to the dual nature of the Archer who symbolizes the sign and who represents the centaur Chiron — a half an, half-horse god who was famed for wisdom and bravery. Sagittarians are often unabashedly optimistic extroverts who draw the admiration and affection of all those they encounter.</item>
        <item>The Goat that symbolizes Capricorn was traditional as half-goat, half-fish. This complex dual nature is echoed in the Capricornian personality, one of the most complex characters in all the zodiac. They have two distinct natures. One side of the sign is ambitious, hard-working, and enterprising. This Capricornian is highly motivated, loves life, and is able to set high but achievable goals. The other side of the Capricornian, however, is lost in a world of real or imagined obstacles to success; further, this Capricornian often cannot find the motivation to take action and challenge those obstacles. Even successful Capricomiars have a tendency to whine and complain about imagined burdens. These darker tendencies are not eased by Capricornians’ introverted natures and love of solitude.</item>
        <item>Often considered the most enigmatic of the zodiac children, Aquarians are fiercely individualistic and independent intellectuals who rarely form permanent relationships with anyone. Nevertheless, they are also noted for being friendly, kind, helpful, and caring; and they are possessed of deep humanitarian instinct. Still, they always remain quintessentially private people. Aquarians are gifted with inventiveness, originality, and creativity, and they are equally comfortable working in such disparate worlds as social work and science.</item>
        <item>Sensitive, sensual, emotional, and richly imaginative and creative, Pisceans are the other-worldly dreamers and poets of the zodiac. Deeply affected by the dual nature of their sign — symbolized by the two fishes swimming in opposite directions. Pisceans are often torn between wanting to do something real and valuable in the world (they are often drawn to humanitarian causes and artistic careers) and retreating from the world altogether to the safer harbours of their private worlds of imagination and dreams. This is an enormous pull for Pisceans, and because of its power, they are often prone to extreme nervous tension and even escapism (sometimes into alcohol and drugs). A lack of self-confidence is almost always at the root of a Piscean‘s inability to get on with the real world, but when this weakness can be overcome, they are found among the finest humanitarians and artists in the world</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>